U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- August, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- September, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- October, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 2, 1967. Item is in English.
- November, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- December, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- January, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 31, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 30, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 24, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 17, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 12, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 8, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 5, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 2, 1968. Item is in English.
- February, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 28, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 26, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 23, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 21, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 16, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 14, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 12, 1968. Item is in English.